[{"_id":1,"user_id":0,"front":"Customer-focused user-facing software","back":"Total","tags":["Mercedes-Benz","Chrysler","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"6/13/2021"},
{"_id":2,"user_id":0,"front":"Digitized fault-tolerant hardware","back":"attitude","tags":["Mercedes-Benz","Cadillac","Nissan"],"date":"4/30/2021"},
{"_id":3,"user_id":1,"front":"Face to face multi-state groupware","back":"Front-line","tags":["Nissan","Buick","Subaru"],"date":"6/19/2021"},
{"_id":4,"user_id":1,"front":"Function-based disintermediate moratorium","back":"projection","tags":["Pontiac","Eagle","GMC"],"date":"4/21/2021"},
{"_id":5,"user_id":0,"front":"Operative heuristic orchestration","back":"5th generation","tags":["Chevrolet","Honda","Jaguar"],"date":"4/26/2021"},
{"_id":6,"user_id":0,"front":"Profound full-range matrices","back":"multimedia","tags":["Kia","Dodge","Ford"],"date":"8/17/2021"},
{"_id":7,"user_id":1,"front":"Progressive holistic website","back":"model","tags":["Chevrolet","Oldsmobile","Cadillac"],"date":"5/10/2021"},
{"_id":8,"user_id":0,"front":"Robust even-keeled algorithm","back":"knowledge user","tags":["Porsche","GMC","Volkswagen"],"date":"4/19/2021"},
{"_id":9,"user_id":1,"front":"Grass-roots clear-thinking policy","back":"Innovative","tags":["CitroÃ«n","Mitsubishi","Saturn"],"date":"6/24/2021"},
{"_id":10,"user_id":1,"front":"Expanded methodical moderator","back":"standardization","tags":["Mitsubishi","Jaguar","Nissan"],"date":"12/30/2020"},
{"_id":11,"user_id":0,"front":"Synergistic 5th generation infrastructure","back":"Enterprise-wide","tags":["Mercedes-Benz","Ford","GMC"],"date":"7/8/2021"},
{"_id":12,"user_id":0,"front":"Secured context-sensitive complexity","back":"Configurable","tags":["Audi","Plymouth","Chevrolet"],"date":"2/14/2021"},
{"_id":13,"user_id":0,"front":"Exclusive mobile frame","back":"Stand-alone","tags":["GMC","Aston Martin","Acura"],"date":"5/26/2021"},
{"_id":14,"user_id":0,"front":"Vision-oriented scalable model","back":"Visionary","tags":["GMC","Volkswagen","Plymouth"],"date":"4/28/2021"},
{"_id":15,"user_id":1,"front":"Enterprise-wide object-oriented encoding","back":"scalable","tags":["Ford","Ferrari","Land Rover"],"date":"12/6/2020"},
{"_id":16,"user_id":1,"front":"Total logistical productivity","back":"data-warehouse","tags":["Chevrolet","Volkswagen","Maybach"],"date":"2/10/2021"},
{"_id":17,"user_id":1,"front":"Sharable hybrid open architecture","back":"migration","tags":["Audi","Pontiac","Mitsubishi"],"date":"9/30/2021"},
{"_id":18,"user_id":0,"front":"Cross-platform global internet solution","back":"Configurable","tags":["Saturn","Ford","Ferrari"],"date":"3/4/2021"},
{"_id":19,"user_id":1,"front":"Implemented 3rd generation customer loyalty","back":"Decentralized","tags":["Ford","Toyota","Oldsmobile"],"date":"7/28/2021"},
{"_id":20,"user_id":0,"front":"Decentralized radical time-frame","back":"encoding","tags":["Chrysler","Mazda","Ford"],"date":"5/19/2021"},
{"_id":21,"user_id":1,"front":"Phased modular contingency","back":"Networked","tags":["Pontiac","Saab","Honda"],"date":"9/15/2021"},
{"_id":22,"user_id":1,"front":"Ergonomic dedicated superstructure","back":"Extended","tags":["Ford","Chevrolet","Honda"],"date":"6/29/2021"},
{"_id":23,"user_id":0,"front":"Fully-configurable human-resource analyzer","back":"encompassing","tags":["GMC","Honda","Volvo"],"date":"6/15/2021"},
{"_id":24,"user_id":0,"front":"Polarised hybrid database","back":"disintermediate","tags":["Audi","MINI","Nissan"],"date":"8/15/2021"},
{"_id":25,"user_id":0,"front":"Optimized eco-centric hierarchy","back":"standardization","tags":["Hyundai","Mitsubishi","Volkswagen"],"date":"3/22/2021"},
{"_id":26,"user_id":1,"front":"Cross-group neutral concept","back":"encoding","tags":["GMC","Jeep","Hyundai"],"date":"3/24/2021"},
{"_id":27,"user_id":1,"front":"Pre-emptive methodical encryption","back":"Triple-buffered","tags":["Ford","Chrysler","Land Rover"],"date":"8/29/2021"},
{"_id":28,"user_id":1,"front":"Face to face fault-tolerant access","back":"budgetary management","tags":["Nissan","Nissan","Mitsubishi"],"date":"2/28/2021"},
{"_id":29,"user_id":1,"front":"Inverse full-range middleware","back":"needs-based","tags":["Volkswagen","Audi","Dodge"],"date":"2/8/2021"},
{"_id":30,"user_id":0,"front":"Customer-focused content-based approach","back":"homogeneous","tags":["Mercury","Ford","Acura"],"date":"6/13/2021"},
{"_id":31,"user_id":1,"front":"Upgradable fault-tolerant moderator","back":"software","tags":["Infiniti","Geo","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"6/5/2021"},
{"_id":32,"user_id":1,"front":"Up-sized executive access","back":"motivating","tags":["BMW","Pontiac","Porsche"],"date":"5/26/2021"},
{"_id":33,"user_id":0,"front":"Profit-focused disintermediate secured line","back":"tangible","tags":["Ford","Toyota","BMW"],"date":"4/20/2021"},
{"_id":34,"user_id":1,"front":"Phased zero administration structure","back":"Team-oriented","tags":["Oldsmobile","Mercury","Mazda"],"date":"8/22/2021"},
{"_id":35,"user_id":1,"front":"Front-line system-worthy application","back":"clear-thinking","tags":["Mitsubishi","Chevrolet","Land Rover"],"date":"5/16/2021"},
{"_id":36,"user_id":1,"front":"Upgradable real-time customer loyalty","back":"Multi-tiered","tags":["Chevrolet","Toyota","Maserati"],"date":"4/24/2021"},
{"_id":37,"user_id":1,"front":"Re-engineered human-resource open architecture","back":"frame","tags":["Volkswagen","Hyundai","Volvo"],"date":"2/2/2021"},
{"_id":38,"user_id":1,"front":"Front-line clear-thinking workforce","back":"multimedia","tags":["Pontiac","Mitsubishi","Dodge"],"date":"1/11/2021"},
{"_id":39,"user_id":0,"front":"Mandatory even-keeled success","back":"concept","tags":["Volkswagen","Mercedes-Benz","Lotus"],"date":"10/27/2021"},
{"_id":40,"user_id":1,"front":"Reduced attitude-oriented process improvement","back":"projection","tags":["Land Rover","Subaru","Volvo"],"date":"8/13/2021"},
{"_id":41,"user_id":0,"front":"Centralized asynchronous algorithm","back":"intranet","tags":["Ford","Mazda","Buick"],"date":"2/22/2021"},
{"_id":42,"user_id":1,"front":"Persevering system-worthy infrastructure","back":"Multi-channelled","tags":["Audi","Acura","Bentley"],"date":"6/26/2021"},
{"_id":43,"user_id":0,"front":"Operative bandwidth-monitored hardware","back":"didactic","tags":["Mitsubishi","Pontiac","Porsche"],"date":"10/31/2021"},
{"_id":44,"user_id":0,"front":"Visionary maximized portal","back":"Reverse-engineered","tags":["Foose","Ford","Hyundai"],"date":"9/2/2021"},
{"_id":45,"user_id":1,"front":"Grass-roots analyzing paradigm","back":"executive","tags":["Acura","Buick","Volkswagen"],"date":"10/31/2021"},
{"_id":46,"user_id":1,"front":"Progressive full-range moratorium","back":"local","tags":["Chrysler","Ford","Toyota"],"date":"8/22/2021"},
{"_id":47,"user_id":0,"front":"Virtual explicit firmware","back":"Grass-roots","tags":["Lexus","Audi","Ford"],"date":"6/19/2021"},
{"_id":48,"user_id":0,"front":"Visionary coherent artificial intelligence","back":"attitude","tags":["BMW","Mazda","Chrysler"],"date":"12/17/2020"},
{"_id":49,"user_id":1,"front":"Programmable actuating concept","back":"Ameliorated","tags":["Lexus","Acura","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"10/10/2021"},
{"_id":50,"user_id":0,"front":"Optimized 6th generation time-frame","back":"Front-line","tags":["Plymouth","Honda","Kia"],"date":"6/19/2021"},
{"_id":51,"user_id":1,"front":"Realigned eco-centric Graphic Interface","back":"methodology","tags":["Volkswagen","Buick","Ford"],"date":"12/2/2020"},
{"_id":52,"user_id":1,"front":"Public-key system-worthy leverage","back":"Function-based","tags":["Ford","GMC","Chevrolet"],"date":"8/27/2021"},
{"_id":53,"user_id":0,"front":"Persevering intermediate access","back":"maximized","tags":["Acura","Volkswagen","Dodge"],"date":"5/23/2021"},
{"_id":54,"user_id":1,"front":"Down-sized 4th generation alliance","back":"adapter","tags":["Toyota","Honda","Honda"],"date":"3/4/2021"},
{"_id":55,"user_id":1,"front":"Reverse-engineered tertiary initiative","back":"attitude-oriented","tags":["Mazda","Dodge","Lexus"],"date":"10/16/2021"},
{"_id":56,"user_id":0,"front":"Organic coherent attitude","back":"implementation","tags":["Jeep","Kia","Dodge"],"date":"9/28/2021"},
{"_id":57,"user_id":1,"front":"Decentralized exuding circuit","back":"conglomeration","tags":["Dodge","Lotus","Toyota"],"date":"2/14/2021"},
{"_id":58,"user_id":0,"front":"Quality-focused uniform product","back":"exuding","tags":["Mazda","Mitsubishi","Porsche"],"date":"8/14/2021"},
{"_id":59,"user_id":1,"front":"Fully-configurable static protocol","back":"migration","tags":["Mercury","Cadillac","Pontiac"],"date":"2/9/2021"},
{"_id":60,"user_id":1,"front":"Mandatory real-time contingency","back":"data-warehouse","tags":["Isuzu","Dodge","Dodge"],"date":"8/11/2021"},
{"_id":61,"user_id":0,"front":"Expanded contextually-based pricing structure","back":"3rd generation","tags":["Lincoln","Buick","Dodge"],"date":"11/12/2020"},
{"_id":62,"user_id":0,"front":"Networked modular protocol","back":"optimal","tags":["Volkswagen","Chevrolet","Ford"],"date":"11/4/2020"},
{"_id":63,"user_id":0,"front":"Profound non-volatile adapter","back":"Team-oriented","tags":["Lexus","Mitsubishi","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"8/19/2021"},
{"_id":64,"user_id":1,"front":"Assimilated fault-tolerant support","back":"database","tags":["Audi","Chevrolet","Oldsmobile"],"date":"12/30/2020"},
{"_id":65,"user_id":0,"front":"Automated demand-driven capacity","back":"Phased","tags":["Nissan","Mercedes-Benz","Hummer"],"date":"4/4/2021"},
{"_id":66,"user_id":1,"front":"Digitized next generation encoding","back":"conglomeration","tags":["Cadillac","Suzuki","Chevrolet"],"date":"2/16/2021"},
{"_id":67,"user_id":0,"front":"Expanded encompassing initiative","back":"well-modulated","tags":["Dodge","Toyota","Acura"],"date":"12/29/2020"},
{"_id":68,"user_id":1,"front":"Innovative tangible contingency","back":"Quality-focused","tags":["Toyota","Lincoln","Maserati"],"date":"11/7/2020"},
{"_id":69,"user_id":1,"front":"Re-contextualized demand-driven algorithm","back":"utilisation","tags":["Chevrolet","Volvo","Mercury"],"date":"4/10/2021"},
{"_id":70,"user_id":0,"front":"Decentralized uniform ability","back":"Phased","tags":["Infiniti","Buick","GMC"],"date":"2/6/2021"},
{"_id":71,"user_id":1,"front":"Compatible system-worthy alliance","back":"Up-sized","tags":["Buick","Plymouth","BMW"],"date":"8/19/2021"},
{"_id":72,"user_id":0,"front":"Visionary 24 hour installation","back":"discrete","tags":["Ford","Ford","Dodge"],"date":"3/21/2021"},
{"_id":73,"user_id":0,"front":"Assimilated national knowledge user","back":"superstructure","tags":["Toyota","Ford","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"4/24/2021"},
{"_id":74,"user_id":1,"front":"Synergistic discrete capacity","back":"algorithm","tags":["Chevrolet","Mitsubishi","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"1/12/2021"},
{"_id":75,"user_id":1,"front":"User-friendly background local area network","back":"Virtual","tags":["Ford","Nissan","Lexus"],"date":"4/4/2021"},
{"_id":76,"user_id":1,"front":"Phased 24 hour benchmark","back":"Intuitive","tags":["Oldsmobile","GMC","BMW"],"date":"9/21/2021"},
{"_id":77,"user_id":1,"front":"Reduced composite task-force","back":"Versatile","tags":["Pontiac","Kia","Chevrolet"],"date":"2/28/2021"},
{"_id":78,"user_id":0,"front":"User-centric regional migration","back":"bottom-line","tags":["Mazda","GMC","Mitsubishi"],"date":"1/2/2021"},
{"_id":79,"user_id":1,"front":"Secured optimal portal","back":"Multi-layered","tags":["Mitsubishi","Mercedes-Benz","Ford"],"date":"9/13/2021"},
{"_id":80,"user_id":1,"front":"Object-based fresh-thinking architecture","back":"context-sensitive","tags":["GMC","Cadillac","Toyota"],"date":"6/21/2021"},
{"_id":81,"user_id":0,"front":"Business-focused 24/7 core","back":"Switchable","tags":["Honda","Mercury","Mazda"],"date":"8/27/2021"},
{"_id":82,"user_id":1,"front":"Open-source client-driven circuit","back":"success","tags":["Toyota","Chevrolet","Mazda"],"date":"4/22/2021"},
{"_id":83,"user_id":1,"front":"Advanced dedicated policy","back":"Future-proofed","tags":["Mazda","Infiniti","Ford"],"date":"2/20/2021"},
{"_id":84,"user_id":1,"front":"Adaptive clear-thinking frame","back":"solution","tags":["Cadillac","Isuzu","Lexus"],"date":"2/13/2021"},
{"_id":85,"user_id":0,"front":"Enterprise-wide solution-oriented workforce","back":"5th generation","tags":["Honda","Ford","Nissan"],"date":"6/20/2021"},
{"_id":86,"user_id":0,"front":"Profit-focused actuating time-frame","back":"capability","tags":["Dodge","Ford","Bentley"],"date":"10/2/2021"},
{"_id":87,"user_id":1,"front":"Synergistic leading edge portal","back":"attitude-oriented","tags":["Holden","Hyundai","Jeep"],"date":"5/26/2021"},
{"_id":88,"user_id":0,"front":"Ergonomic bi-directional knowledge user","back":"content-based","tags":["Jaguar","Suzuki","Mazda"],"date":"11/14/2020"},
{"_id":89,"user_id":0,"front":"Enterprise-wide clear-thinking success","back":"secured line","tags":["GMC","Ford","Mercedes-Benz"],"date":"1/21/2021"},
{"_id":90,"user_id":0,"front":"Re-engineered uniform hardware","back":"regional","tags":["Mazda","Chevrolet","Pontiac"],"date":"9/18/2021"},
{"_id":91,"user_id":1,"front":"Reverse-engineered regional throughput","back":"6th generation","tags":["Porsche","Saab","Subaru"],"date":"6/30/2021"},
{"_id":92,"user_id":0,"front":"Monitored optimal moratorium","back":"internet solution","tags":["Audi","Buick","Chevrolet"],"date":"9/2/2021"},
{"_id":93,"user_id":0,"front":"Business-focused bi-directional alliance","back":"clear-thinking","tags":["Corbin","Acura","Dodge"],"date":"10/5/2021"},
{"_id":94,"user_id":1,"front":"Up-sized secondary challenge","back":"application","tags":["Infiniti","Suzuki","Acura"],"date":"6/9/2021"},
{"_id":95,"user_id":1,"front":"Phased bottom-line frame","back":"contingency","tags":["Volvo","Toyota","Acura"],"date":"7/21/2021"},
{"_id":96,"user_id":1,"front":"Synchronised 24/7 knowledge base","back":"human-resource","tags":["Suzuki","Hyundai","Ford"],"date":"8/4/2021"},
{"_id":97,"user_id":0,"front":"Profound 5th generation knowledge user","back":"asymmetric","tags":["Chevrolet","Volvo","BMW"],"date":"8/26/2021"},
{"_id":98,"user_id":0,"front":"Mandatory disintermediate paradigm","back":"instruction set","tags":["Nissan","Toyota","Tesla"],"date":"10/4/2021"},
{"_id":99,"user_id":0,"front":"Organized tangible complexity","back":"portal","tags":["Spyker","Lexus","Audi"],"date":"3/26/2021"},
{"_id":100,"user_id":0,"front":"Triple-buffered cohesive budgetary management","back":"Phased","tags":["Jeep","Mitsubishi","Rambler"],"date":"8/3/2021"}]